{
    "Questions": [
        {
          "question":       "why Tarzan is better than you (Tilak) ?",
          "optionOne":      "He had a girlfriend!",
          "optionTwo":      "He does not look like a dick!",
          "optionThree":    "Because he can hold tree roots with his ass crack",
          "optionFour":     "So what mama, even I have pogo!",
          "rightAnswer":    "optionFour",
          "audiencePoll":   "5, 10, 5, 80, 0",
          "amount":         "5,000",
          "information":    "Tilak üòç: Whenever I see her shaving her armpit's hair, I get an erection mama!"
        },
        {
            "question":    "What did Tilak do when he got to know that madam is infected with HIV-AIDS ?",
            "optionOne":   "Ayyo! that's why that bhosdi waali leaked like jog falls!",
            "optionTwo":   "Haah bro! I'm a genius! I will chop off my dick!",
            "optionThree": "Started thinking that by now, he must have passed on AIDS to Pogo, Bade dil waali and Varun!",
            "optionFour":  "Will see a doctor after he finishes Batch Printing in DocStar ü§¢",
            "rightAnswer": "optionThree",
            "audiencePoll":"20, 5, 65, 15, 0",
            "amount":      "10,000",
            "information": "Tilak üòí: Poor pogo could have saved herself, had she not been drinking my breast milk!"
        },
        {
            "question":    "Why Tilak has smelling disorder ?",
            "optionOne":   "Because he uses Rubini Omkumar's panty as Corona mask!",
            "optionTwo":   "BGW or Senior Pogo farted on his face when he was cleaning her ass by his tongue",
            "optionThree": "Pogo uses Tilak's hand for scratching her jhaants and then he smells it",
            "optionFour":  "Bhenchod! ye kya options hain!",
            "rightAnswer": "optionOne",
            "audiencePoll":"65, 5, 15, 5, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": "Tilak ü§¶‚Äç‚ôÇÔ∏è: I had a headache when I tasted that salty and bushy pussy. My god it stinks!"
        },
        {
            "question":    "What is Tilak's idea of masturbation ?",
            "optionOne":   "He asks Kukkutpalli to open his mouth",
            "optionTwo":   "He digs a hole in the trunk of trees!",
            "optionThree": "Chaudhry's ass is too big mama",
            "optionFour":  "He is so flexible that he gives a self blowjob!",
            "rightAnswer": "optionTwo",
            "audiencePoll":"5, 90, 3, 2, 0",
            "amount":      "40,000",
            "information": "Tilak üíã: Masturbation is an art which is devoid of real time attachments!"
        },
        {
            "question":    "Who does Tilak think as the most haraami guy he's ever met ?",
            "optionOne":   "‡§Ü‡§®‡§Ç‡§¶",
            "optionTwo":   "‡§∏‡•Å‡§Æ‡§ø‡§§",
            "optionThree": "‡§™‡§Ç‡§°‡§ø‡§§, ‡§™‡§Ç‡§°‡§ø‡§§, ‡§™‡§Ç‡§°‡§ø‡§§",
            "optionFour":  "Mama, your choice this one is correct!",
            "rightAnswer": "optionFour",
            "audiencePoll":"12, 18, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "80,000",
            "information": "Tilak üê±‚ÄçüöÄ: All are haraami's mama! difficult to choose biggest pig from plethora of pigs!"
        },
        {
            "question":    "Which one of the four alternatives Tilak will choose ?",
            "optionOne":   "He wants one hand on keyboard and other inside Rubini Omkumar's chaddi",
            "optionTwo":   "Licking Wrestler's pussy!",
            "optionThree": "‡§ï‡•Å‡§ï‡•ç‡§ï‡•Å‡§ü‡§™‡§≤‡•ç‡§≤‡•Ä ‡§ï‡•á ‡§∏‡§æ‡§• ‡§ö‡•Å‡§Æ‡•ç‡§¨‡§®",
            "optionFour":  "My camera girl needs me mama!",
            "rightAnswer": "optionFour",
            "audiencePoll":"8, 5, 25, 62, 0",
            "amount":      "1,60,000",
            "information": "Tilak ü§≥: Mama, She deserves to sit on the business end of my dick!"
        },
        {
            "question":    "What would be the weight of dumb-bell that Tilak uses for his dick muscles ?",
            "optionOne":   "He can't as he has erectile dysfunctionality",
            "optionTwo":   "He gets tired after lifting 2 pieces of cardomom from his dick",
            "optionThree": "He thinks there is no point, Pogo has a bigger dick!",
            "optionFour":  "I am a part-timer in majestic mama, why I will workout my dick!",
            "rightAnswer": "optionOne",
            "audiencePoll":"78, 12, 5, 5, 0",
            "amount":      "3,20,000",
            "information": "Tilak üéÉ: ‚Çπ 200 a day in Majestic. My life rocks mama!"
        },
        {
            "question":    "‡§Ø‡§¶‡§ø ‡§™‡§Ç‡§°‡§ø‡§§ ‡§ï‡•ã ‡§Æ‡•à‡§°‡§Æ ‡§ï‡§æ ‡§≤‡•å‡•ú‡§æ ‡§®‡§æ‡§™‡§®‡•á ‡§ï‡•á ‡§≤‡§ø‡§è ‡§ï‡§π‡§æ ‡§ú‡§æ‡§è ‡§§‡•ã ‡§µ‡•ã ‡§ï‡•ç‡§Ø‡§æ ‡§ï‡§∞‡•á‡§ó‡§æ ?",
            "optionOne":   "‡§Ü‡§§‡•ç‡§Æ‡§π‡§§‡•ç‡§Ø‡§æ",
            "optionTwo":   "‡§∞‡•á‡§∏‡§≤‡§∞ ‡§∏‡•á ‡§â‡§∏‡§ï‡•á ‡§Æ‡•Å‡§Å‡§π ‡§ï‡•Ä ‡§ó‡§π‡§∞‡§æ‡§à ‡§™‡•Ç‡§õ‡•á‡§ó‡§æ",
            "optionThree": "‡§Æ‡•à‡§°‡§Æ ‡§ï‡•Ä ‡§°‡•á‡§∏‡•ç‡§ï ‡§ï‡•á ‡§õ‡•á‡§¶ ‡§Æ‡•á‡§Ç ‡§∏‡•ç‡§ï‡•á‡§≤ ‡§°‡§æ‡§≤ ‡§ï‡•á ‡§®‡§æ‡§™‡•á‡§ó‡§æ",
            "optionFour":  "‡§Æ‡•à‡§Ø‡•ç‡§Ø‡§æ ‡§ï‡•Ä ‡§ö‡•Ç‡§§ ‡§¨‡§æ‡§¨‡§æ ‡§ï‡•ç‡§Ø‡§æ ‡§π‡•à ‡§Ø‡•á",
            "rightAnswer": "optionOne",
            "audiencePoll":"42, 8, 15, 15, 20",
            "amount":      "6,40,000",
            "information": "‡§™‡§ø‡§§‡§æ ‡§™‡§∞ ‡§™‡•Ç‡§§, ‡§ú‡§æ‡§§ ‡§Æ‡•á‡§Ç ‡§ò‡•ã‡§°‡§æ, ‡§®‡§π‡•Ä‡§Ç ‡§¶‡•á‡§ñ‡§æ ‡§ú‡§æ‡§è‡§ó‡§æ ‡§Æ‡•à‡§°‡§Æ ‡§ú‡•à‡§∏‡§æ ‡§≤‡•å‡•ú‡§æ"
        },
        {
            "question":    "‡§ï‡•Å‡§∞‡•ç‡§∞ ‡§ï‡•Å‡§∞‡•ç‡§∞ ‡§ï‡•Ä ‡§ß‡•ç‡§µ‡§®‡§ø ‡§ï‡§æ ‡§Ö‡§∏‡§≤‡•Ä ‡§ï‡§æ‡§∞‡§£ ‡§ï‡•ç‡§Ø‡§æ ‡§∞‡§π‡§æ ‡§π‡•ã‡§ó‡§æ ?",
            "optionOne":   "‡§ù‡§æ‡§Ç‡§ü‡•ã‡§Ç ‡§Æ‡•á‡§Ç ‡§´‡§Ç‡§∏‡§æ ‡§Æ‡•à‡§≤",
            "optionTwo":   "‡§ù‡§æ‡§Ç‡§ü ‡§î‡§∞ ‡§®‡§æ‡§ñ‡•Ç‡§® ‡§ï‡•á ‡§Æ‡§ß‡•ç‡§Ø ‡§ò‡§∞‡•ç‡§∑‡§£",
            "optionThree": "‡§ñ‡•Å‡§ú‡§≤‡•Ä ‡§ï‡•á ‡§∏‡§æ‡§• ‡§ó‡•Ä‡§≤‡•á ‡§™‡§æ‡§¶ ‡§ï‡•Ä ‡§ß‡•ç‡§µ‡§®‡§ø",
            "optionFour":  "‡§Ø‡•á ‡§ï‡•á‡§µ‡§≤ ‡§™‡§Ç‡§°‡§ø‡§§ ‡§ï‡•Ä ‡§™‡§∞‡§ø‡§ï‡§≤‡•ç‡§™‡§®‡§æ",
            "rightAnswer": "optionTwo",
            "audiencePoll":"8, 80, 8, 2, 2",
            "amount":      "12,50,000",
            "information": "‡§ï‡§à ‡§¶‡§ø‡§®‡•ã‡§Ç ‡§§‡§ï ‡§∏‡•ç‡§®‡§æ‡§® ‡§®‡§æ ‡§ï‡§∞‡§®‡•á ‡§∏‡•á ‡§ù‡§æ‡§Ç‡§ü‡•ã‡§Ç ‡§Æ‡•á‡§Ç ‡§Æ‡•à‡§≤ ‡§â‡§§‡•ç‡§™‡§®‡•ç‡§® ‡§π‡•ã ‡§ú‡§æ‡§§‡§æ ‡§π‡•à ‡§ú‡§ø‡§∏‡§ï‡•á ‡§ï‡§æ‡§∞‡§£ ‡§ù‡§æ‡§Ç‡§ü‡•á‡§Ç ‡§Ö‡§™‡§®‡§æ ‡§®‡•à‡§∏‡§∞‡•ç‡§ó‡§ø‡§ï ‡§ï‡§æ‡§≤‡§æ ‡§∞‡§Ç‡§ó ‡§§‡•ç‡§Ø‡§æ‡§ó ‡§ï‡§∞ ‡§≠‡•Ç‡§∞‡•á ‡§∞‡§Ç‡§ó ‡§Æ‡•á‡§Ç ‡§™‡§∞‡§ø‡§µ‡§∞‡•ç‡§§‡§ø‡§§ ‡§π‡•ã ‡§ú‡§æ‡§§‡•Ä ‡§π‡•à‡§Ç ‡§è‡§µ‡§Ç ‡§®‡§æ‡§ñ‡•Ç‡§®‡•ã‡§Ç ‡§ï‡•á ‡§∏‡§Ç‡§™‡§∞‡•ç‡§ï ‡§Æ‡•á‡§Ç ‡§Ü‡§ï‡§∞ ‡§ï‡•Å‡§∞‡•ç‡§∞ ‡§ï‡•Å‡§∞‡•ç‡§∞ ‡§ï‡•Ä ‡§ß‡•ç‡§µ‡§®‡§ø ‡§â‡§§‡•ç‡§™‡§®‡•ç‡§® ‡§ï‡§∞‡§§‡•Ä ‡§π‡•à‡§Ç!"
        },
        {
            "question":    "‡§ï‡•ç‡§Ø‡•ã‡§Ç ‡§™‡§Ç‡§°‡§ø‡§§ ‡§®‡•á ‡§ò‡§∞ ‡§™‡•á ‡§Æ‡§æ‡§á‡§ï‡•ç‡§∞‡•ã‡§∏‡•ç‡§ï‡•ã‡§™ ‡§∞‡§ñ‡§æ ‡§π‡•à ?",
            "optionOne":   "‡§ï‡•ã‡§à ‡§ï‡§æ‡§∞‡§£ ‡§®‡§π‡•Ä‡§Ç! ‡§Æ‡•á‡§∞‡•Ä ‡§Æ‡§∞‡•ç‡•õ‡•Ä",
            "optionTwo":   "‡§ï‡•Å‡§ï‡•ç‡§ï‡•Å‡§ü‡§™‡§≤‡•ç‡§≤‡•Ä ‡§ï‡§æ ‡§ö‡•Å‡§Æ‡•ç‡§Æ‡§æ ‡§≤‡•á‡§§‡•á ‡§µ‡•ò‡•ç‡§§ ‡§â‡§∏‡§ï‡•Ä ‡•õ‡§¨‡§æ‡§® ‡§™‡•á ‡§≤‡§ó‡•Ä ‡§ù‡§æ‡§Ç‡§ü ‡§¢‡•Ç‡§Ç‡§¢‡•á‡§Ç ‡§ï‡•á ‡§≤‡§ø‡§è",
            "optionThree": "‡§Æ‡•Å‡§† ‡§Æ‡§æ‡§∞‡§®‡•á ‡§ï‡•Ä ‡§á‡§ö‡•ç‡§õ‡§æ ‡§π‡•ã‡§®‡•á ‡§™‡§∞ ‡§≤‡§®‡•ç‡§° ‡§¢‡•Ç‡§Ç‡§¢‡§®‡•á ‡§ï‡•á ‡§≤‡§ø‡§è",
            "optionFour":  "‡§ï‡•ã‡§à ‡§Æ‡•Å‡§ù‡•á ‡§Æ‡§æ‡§∞ ‡§π‡•Ä ‡§¶‡•ã ‡§ú‡§æ‡§® ‡§∏‡•á",
            "rightAnswer": "optionThree",
            "audiencePoll":"2, 6, 88, 1, 3",
            "amount":      "25 Lakh",
            "information": "‡§á‡§∏‡§ï‡§æ ‡§ï‡•ã‡§à ‡§µ‡§ø‡§∂‡•ç‡§≤‡•á‡§∑‡§£ ‡§®‡§π‡•Ä‡§Ç ‡§π‡•à , ‡§¨‡§∏ ‡§Æ‡•õ‡•á ‡§≤‡•ã"
        },
        {
            "question":    "‡§™‡§Ç‡§°‡§ø‡§§ ‡§ï‡•á ‡§™‡§æ‡§á‡§•‡§® ‡§∏‡•á ‡§ï‡•ç‡§Ø‡§æ ‡§§‡§æ‡§§‡•ç‡§™‡§∞‡•ç‡§Ø ‡§π‡•à ?",
            "optionOne":   "‡§ö‡•Ç‡§§ ‡§ï‡§æ ‡§™‡•Å‡§≤‡•ç‡§≤‡§ø‡§Ç‡§ó ‡§∏‡§Æ‡§ï‡§ï‡•ç‡§∑",
            "optionTwo":   "‡§∏‡•â‡§´‡•ç‡§ü‡§µ‡•á‡§Ø‡§∞ ‡§®‡§ø‡§∑‡•ç‡§™‡§æ‡§¶‡§® ‡§Æ‡•á‡§Ç ‡§∏‡§π‡§æ‡§Ø‡§ï ‡§µ‡§ø‡§ß‡§ø",
            "optionThree": "‡§≤‡§®‡•ç‡§°, ‡§≤‡•å‡•ú‡§æ, ‡§≤‡§ø‡§Ç‡§ó - ‡§∞‡•Ç‡§™ ‡§è‡§ï, ‡§®‡§æ‡§Æ ‡§Ö‡§®‡•á‡§ï",
            "optionFour":  "‡§∏‡§≠‡•Ä ‡§§‡•Ä‡§®‡•ã‡§Ç",
            "rightAnswer": "optionFour",
            "audiencePoll":"12, 5, 5, 78, 0",
            "amount":      "50 Lakh",
            "information": "‡§Ö‡§®‡•á‡§ï‡§§‡§æ ‡§Æ‡•á‡§Ç ‡§è‡§ï‡§§‡§æ ‡§≤‡•å‡•ú‡•á ‡§ï‡•Ä ‡§µ‡§ø‡§∂‡•á‡§∑‡§§‡§æ‡•§ ‡§∞‡§Ç‡§ó ‡§Ö‡§®‡•á‡§ï ‡§Æ‡•Å‡§ü‡•ç‡§†‡•Ä ‡§è‡§ï!"
        },
        {
            "question":    "What does Tilak like to take ?",
            "optionOne":   "Johnson ki choot jaisi shakal ki chummi",
            "optionTwo":   "Choot ke paani se bheega hua Varun ka Lund!",
            "optionThree": "Madam ke laudey se nikla moot jaisa peela paani",
            "optionFour":  "Pogo channel ki sookhi hui choot jismain ek baar lund daalne se chilaa jaaye!",
            "rightAnswer": "optionFour",
            "audiencePoll":"12, 15, 15, 58, 0",
            "amount":      "1 Crore",
            "information": "Tilak : Is sansaar mein choot se bada koi dharm nahi aur sookhi choot ko chilne jaisi badi koi ibaadat nahi!"
        },
        {
            "question":    "Tilak kya mooh mein leke nahi bolta hai ?",
            "optionOne":   "madam ka lauda!",
            "optionTwo":   "Johnson ka Lehsun",
            "optionThree": "Varun ki moong-fali",
            "optionFour":  "Main apna hi din bhar mooh mein liye ghoomta hum",
            "rightAnswer": "optionThree",
            "audiencePoll":"5, 18, 60, 15, 5",
            "amount":      "3 Crore",
            "information": "Tilak üòõ: What to tell you guys, I am very flexible."
        },
        {
            "question":    "Which one is the religious tallest minar in India ?",
            "optionOne":   "Fateh Burj",
            "optionTwo":   "Qutub Minar",
            "optionThree": "Chand Minar",
            "optionFour":  "Shaheed Minar",
            "rightAnswer": "optionOne",
            "audiencePoll":"50, 15, 10, 15, 10",
            "amount":      "5 Crore",
            "information": "The Fateh Burj (English: The Victory Tower) is the tallest religious minar in India situated in the historical village of Chappar Chiri in the SAS Nagar district, Punjab. It was completed in 2011."
        },
        {
            "question":    "With how many countries India share its land borders ?",
            "optionOne":   "5",
            "optionTwo":   "6",
            "optionThree": "7",
            "optionFour":  "8",
            "rightAnswer": "optionTwo",
            "audiencePoll":"5, 90, 3, 2, 0",
            "amount":      "7 Crore",
            "information": "Inventor Ralph Baer, The 'Father Of Video Games,' Dies At 92. German-American game developer Ralph Baer shows the prototype of the first games console which was invented by him during a press conference on the Games Convention Online in Leipzig, Germany in 2009."

        }
      ]
    }